NEW WALLET, HUH?
YEAH, IT WAS TIME.
THE OLD CONDOM RING
IN THE LEATHER
JUST DOESN'T SAY "COOL"
ANYMORE, YOU KNOW?
RACHEL, YOU JUST
PUT AN EMPTY CARTON
BACK IN THE FRIDGE.
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT THE GARBAGE
WAS FULL.
HAVE YOU EVER
TAKEN OUT THE TRASH?
WELL, I, UH... THOUGHT
YOU LIKED DOING IT.
THIRD DOOR ON THE LEFT.
RIGHT.
OH, HEY, MR. TREEGER.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM...
OH! OH!
SORRY.
IT'S A LITTLE OLD,
BUT...
YOU'RE CLOGGING UP
THE CHUTE
I JUST SPENT
A HALF HOUR UNCLOGGING.
OH, I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T...
I DON'T COME
IN HERE A LOT.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T.
'CAUSE YOU'RE
A LITTLE PRINCESS.
"DADDY,
BUY ME A PIZZA."
"DADDY, BUY ME
A CANDY FACTORY."
"DADDY, MAKE
THE CAST OF CATS
SING 'HAPPY BIRTHDAY'
TO ME."
BUT I...
YOU THINK YOU CAN
JUST MAKE A MESS
THE BIG MAN
IN THE COVERALLS
WILL COME AND
CLEAN IT UP, HUH?
WHY DON'T YOU THINK
OF SOMEONE ELSE
FOR A CHANGE?
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
( sobbing )
GOD! IF YOU'RE GOING
TO CRY ABOUT IT...
( crying )
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
WHOA! TREEGER
MADE YOU CRY?
YES.
HE SAID
REALLY MEAN THINGS
THAT WERE
ONLY PARTLY TRUE.
I'M GOING DOWN THERE
AND TEACH THAT GUY A LESSON.
PLEASE, IT'S BEST
IF WE FORGET ABOUT IT.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU WEREN'T ALMOST JUST KILLED.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
SCHOOL IS IN SESSION!
YOU GUYS,
IS THIS A GYM CARD?
OH, YEAH.
GYM MEMBER.
I TRY TO GO
FOUR TIMES A WEEK
BUT I'VE MISSED
THE LAST 1,200 TIMES.
SO WHY DON'T
YOU QUIT?
YOU DON'T THINK I'VE TRIED?
YOU THINK I LIKE
HAVING $50 TAKEN OUT
OF MY BANK ACCOUNT EVERY MONTH?
THEY MAKE YOU GO
ALL THE WAY DOWN THERE.
THEN THEY USE ALL
THESE PHRASES AND PEPPINESS
TO TRY TO CONFUSE YOU.
AND THEN THEY BRING OUT MARIA.
WHO IS MARIA?
AH, MARIA...
YOU CAN'T SAY NO TO HER.
SHE'S LIKE THIS LYCRA,
SPANDEX-COVERED GYM TREAT.
YOU NEED ME
TO GO DOWN THERE WITH YOU
AND HOLD YOUR HAND?
NO.
YOU'RE STRONG ENOUGH
TO FACE HER ALONE?
OH, NO.
YOU'LL
HAVE TO COME.
OH, TRIBBIANI. HMM.
HOLD ON.
I'LL GET THE PLUNGER.
HEY, YOU HOLD ON, PAL.
NOW, YOU MADE
MY FRIEND RACHEL CRY
SO NOW YOU'RE GOING
TO GO UP THERE
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO APOLOGIZE TO HER
UNLESS YOU WANT ME
TO CALL THE LANDLORD.
AND TELL HIM WHAT?
MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
OF "NOT MAKING GIRLS CRY."
OF A LITTLE SOMETHING
CALLED "THE RENT
STABILIZATION ACT OF 1968."
I HAVE ACTUALLY
NOT HEARD OF THAT.
YEAH? WELL, YOUR FRIENDS
ARE IN VIOLATION OF IT.
I BEEN A NICE GUY
UP UNTIL NOW
BUT I DON'T
NEED THIS GRIEF.
I'M GOING
TO CALL THE LANDLORD
AND TELL HIM THAT MONICA
IS ILLEGALLY SUBLETTING
HER GRANDMOTHER'S
APARTMENT.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE
OUT OF HERE, PAL.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
SOMETHING I DON'T KNOW?
PLEASE, SOMEBODY TELL ME
I DON'T HAVE TO WORK TODAY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MY FIRST MASSAGE
IS THIS INCREDIBLY GORGEOUS GUY
AND EVERY TIME I SEE HIM
I JUST WANT TO DO THINGS TO HIM
THAT I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO CHARGE FOR.
SO DO THEM FOR FREE.
OH, NO. IT IS FORBIDDEN.
NO, NO. MRS. CARTER FIRES PEOPLE
FOR MESSING AROUND WITH CLIENTS.
AND IT'S AGAINST MY OATH
AS A MASSEUSE.
THEY MAKE YOU
TAKE AN OATH?
NO. I MADE MYSELF TAKE ONE.
YEAH, NO FOOLING AROUND
WITH CLIENTS
AND, UM... ALWAYS BE PREPARED.
THAT ONE'S ACTUALLY
FROM THE BOY SCOUTS
BUT IT JUST MAKES GOOD SENSE.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GIVE HIM
TO SOMEBODY ELSE?
NO, I CAN HANDLE IT.
NO, I'M A PROFESSIONAL.
OH, PHEEBS, IS THAT
A NEW ANKLE BRACELET?
AND YOU GOT
A PEDICURE.
YOUR FEET
ARE ALL DRESSED UP.
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY
PART OF YOU HE CAN SEE
WHEN HE'S
ON THE TABLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO
SOME FEET FLIRTING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THEN HOW DO YOU
EXPLAIN THE TOE RING?
BECAUSE IT'S ARABIAN PRINCESS
DAY AT WORK, OKAY?
LEAVE ME ALONE.
OH!
MY HERO!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, UH...
I WENT DOWN
AND TOLD HIM
NO ONE TREATS
MY FRIENDS LIKE THAT
AND HE'D BETTER COME UP HERE
AND APOLOGIZE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
UH... HE SAID HE WASN'T
GOING TO APOLOGIZE
BECAUSE YOU GUYS
ARE LIVING HERE ILLEGALLY.
INSTEAD, WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO
IS HAVE YOU EVICTED.
WHAT?
EVICTED?
I TOLD YOU NOT
TO GO DOWN THERE.
LOOK, HE MADE RACHEL CRY!
RACHEL ALWAYS CRIES!
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
( crying )
JOEY, YOU GO DOWN THERE
AND YOU
SUCK UP TO HIM.
I MEAN, YOU SUCK
LIKE YOU'VE NEVER
SUCKED BEFORE!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TRY.
BUT IF I CAN'T,
YOU STAY WITH CHANDLER AND I
UNTIL YOU GET SETTLED.
GO!
I'LL CHECK
WITH HIM FIRST
BUT I THINK HE'LL BE COOL.
JOEY!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
NOW REMEMBER WHAT
WE TALKED ABOUT:
YOU GOT TO BE STRONG.
YES. YES.
NOW ONE MORE TIME:
"HEY, DON'T YOU WANT
A WASHBOARD STOMACH
AND ROCK-HARD PECS?"
NO. I WANT
A FLABBY GUT
AND SAGGY MAN-BREASTS.
GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
YOU WANT TO QUIT?
YOU DO REALIZE
YOU WON'T HAVE ACCESS
TO OUR NEW
FULL-SERVICE SWEDISH SPA?
( forceful grunt )
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
OKAY. DAVE, IN THE MEMBERSHIP
OFFICE, HANDLES QUITTERS.
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU A MEMBER?
ME?
NO.
SORRY. MEMBERS ONLY.
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
IT'S OKAY, MAN.
BE STRONG.
( forceful grunt )
SO, ARE YOU
A MEMBER OF ANY GYM?
NO, AND I'M
NOT GOING TO BE
SO YOU CAN SAVE
YOUR LITTLE SPEECH.
OKAY. NO PROBLEM.
COULD YOU COME HERE
FOR A SECOND?
HI. I'M MARIA.
I'M...
WOW, YOU HAVE
REALLY PRETTY FEET.
THESE OLD THINGS?
WOULD YOU SPEND SOME TIME
ON MY SCIATIC AREA?
IT'S BEEN KILLING ME TODAY.
YOU MEAN THE...
BY "SCIATIC,"
TOWEL-COVERED
PORTION.
YEAH.
SURE. YEAH. NO, I CAN DO THAT...
YEAH. BECAUSE, UH...
YOU KNOW, USUALLY
THE MUSCLES IN THE SCIATIC AREA
CAN GET, YOU KNOW,
REAL NICE AND TIGHT.
YEAH. SO, UM.... TELL ME, RICK
HOW, UM... HOW DID YOU
INJURE THE AREA?
OH, A 16-HOUR SIT-IN
FOR GREENPEACE.
OH.
OW!
DID YOU
JUST BITE ME?
NO.
WHAT?
PLEASE DON'T KICK
MONICA AND RACHEL OUT.
THIS WASN'T THEIR FAULT.
IT WAS MINE.
SHOULD I KICK YOU
GUYS OUT INSTEAD?
NO. YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WHERE WOULD THE CHICK
AND THE DUCK LIVE?
YOU HAVE PETS?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THOSE ARE, UH... NICKNAMES.
YEAH, I'M THE CHICK
AND CHANDLER'S THE DUCK.
HUH. I WOULD
HAVE THOUGHT
IT WAS THE OTHER
WAY AROUND.
COME ON, MAN.
JUST... JUST
LET THE GIRLS STAY.
I'LL DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
REALLY?
YOU'D DO ANYTHING?
YEAH, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY.
I GOT SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
CAN YOU BE
MY DANCING PARTNER?
THAT'S NOT
PRISON LINGO, IS IT?
HIS DANCING PARTNER?
YEAH.
THERE'S THIS
SUPERINTENDENTS' DANCE--
THE SUPER BALL...
AND HE WANTS TO IMPRESS MARGE
THIS LADY SUPER
THAT HE'S GOT A CRUSH ON.
WHY DOESN'T HE JUST
PRACTICE WITH A GIRL?
HE'S TOO SHY.
HE DOESN'T THINK
HE'S GOOD ENOUGH
TO DANCE WITH GIRLS YET.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HE ALMOST DANCED ME
RIGHT DOWN THAT...
GARBAGE CHUTE.
OH, WOULD YOU LET
IT GO, ALREADY?
YOU'RE FINE.
HEY.
SO DID YOU QUIT?
NO. I ALMOST DID.
COULDN'T LEAVE ROSS THERE
WITHOUT A SPOTTER.
WAIT, NOW, SO YOU
JOINED THE GYM?
( laughing )
OH...
AND THAT'S FUNNY WHY?
OH, UM...
I WAS JUST, YOU KNOW,
PICTURING YOU
WORKING OUT, AND, UM...
OH, THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DOOMED, OKAY?
THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE
50 BUCKS A MONTH
OUT OF OUR ACCOUNTS
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
YOU COULD ACTUALLY
GO TO THE GYM.
( laughing )
OR...
OR WE COULD GO TO THE BANK
CLOSE OUR ACCOUNTS
AND CUT THEM OFF AT THE SOURCE.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
OH, MAN, BUT THEN
WE WON'T BE BANK BUDDIES.
NOW THERE'S TWO REASONS.
HEY.
OH, YOU GUYS.
REMEMBER THAT CUTE CLIENT
I TOLD YOU ABOUT?
I BIT HIM.
WHERE?
ON THE TUSHIE.
AND THAT'S NOT AGAINST
YOUR OATH?
NO. I KNOW.
I'M SORRY,
BUT THE MOMENT I TOUCH HIM
I JUST WANT
TO THROW OUT MY OLD OATH
AND TAKE A NEW DIRTY ONE.
WELL, NEXT TIME
YOU'RE MASSAGING HIM
YOU SHOULD TRY
TO DISTRACT YOURSELF.
YEAH, YEAH.
LIKE, WHEN I'M DOING
SOMETHING EXCITING
AND I DON'T WANT
TO GET TOO... EXCITED
I JUST TRY AND THINK
OF OTHER THINGS
LIKE, UH, SANDWICHES
AND, UH, BASEBALL
AND, UH...
CHANDLER.
THANK YOU, JOEY.
OH, NO. THANK YOU.
( knocking on door )
ALL RIGHT, I'M HERE.
LET'S, UH,
GET THIS OVER WITH.
OKAY, WELL
JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
( '30s dance music playing )
DON'T WE NEED TO DO SOME KIND
OF PREPARATION FIRST
LIKE, UH, GET REALLY DRUNK?
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
JUST PUT YOUR
ARMS AROUND ME.
YEAH.
I-I-I'M SORRY.
NO, IT'S OKAY
BUT IF I'M MARGE
MY BREASTS ARE COMING
OUT MY BACK.
AH, FORGET IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE
ANY GOOD AT THIS.
MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
( music stops )
I'M JUST A BIG POTATO
WITH ARMS AND LEGS AND A HEAD.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU'RE NOT A... POTATO.
I'M SURE AS HELL NOT A DANCER.
IT'S NO USE.
MARGE WILL NEVER GO FOR ME.
AH, COME ON, TREEGER.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU JUST, UH...
YOU JUST NEED MORE PRACTICE.
HERE. COME ON.
LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
( music starts )
COME ON.
PLUS, IT WAS PROBABLY
MOSTLY MY FAULT.
I MEAN, I'M NOT
REALLY THAT COMFORTABLE
DANCING WITH A...
WHOO-HOO!
HEY!
YEAH!
( sighs )
SO HOW GOES THE DANCING?
GAY YET?
HA, HA, HA.
YOU GUYS OWE ME BIG TIME.
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT?
YOU JUST DID A
LITTLE DANCE-Y THING.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU DID, LIKE,
A LITTLE HOP.
YOU ARE SO
ENJOYING THIS.
NO, I'M NOT.
AND IT WASN'T A HOP.
IT WAS A PAUX DE BARRE.
OH!
( both laughing )
YOU KNOW THE WORDS!
YOU ARE SO INTO THIS.
ALL RIGHT. MAYBE I'M
ENJOYING IT A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN, I'M GETTING
PRETTY GOOD AT IT.
OH, THIS IS SO SWEET.
JOEY, OUR LITTLE
TWINKLE-TOES.
HEY, HEY. HOLD ON.
THIS ISN'T SOME KIND
OF GIRLIE DANCE.
IT'S LIKE A SPORT.
IT'S MANLY.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, COME HERE.
SHOW ME SOME MANLY MOVES.
ALL RIGHT.
( giggles )
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO LEAD.
HELLO.
HI.
WE'D LIKE TO CLOSE
OUR ACCOUNTS.
CLOSE YOUR ACCOUNTS?
IS THERE SOME PROBLEM?
NO, NO.
NO. WE'D JUST LIKE
TO CLOSE THEM.
OKAY.
MS. LAMBERT HANDLES
ALL OUR CLOSURES.
WOULD YOU COME OVER HERE
PLEASE?
HI. I'M KAREN.
I WANT TO QUIT THE BANK!
OKAY, BASEBALL.
RICK PLAYING BASEBALL.
OKAY, HE SLIDES INTO SECOND.
MAYBE EVEN HIS PANTS
COME DOWN A LITTLE.
OH, NO! WAIT! NO!
NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT,
SANDWICHES, SANDWICHES.
UM, OKAY, ON A PLATE.
MAYBE RICK'S PANTS
COME DOWN A LITTLE.
NO, NO!
CHANDLER.
OKAY, CHANDLER.
OOH, THAT'S WORKING.
CHANDLER'S... KNEES.
CHANDLER'S ANKLES.
CHANDLER'S ANKLE HAIR.
OH, NO.
OKAY, YOU'RE ALL SET.
OH, WOW.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WAS THAT REALLY
JUST AN HOUR?
YEAH...
IN REALLY LONG HOUR WORLD.
WHAT?
( sighs ):
OKAY.
I HAVE AN ENORMOUS
CRUSH ON YOU
BUT BECAUSE YOU'RE A CLIENT,
I CAN'T ASK YOU OUT
EVEN THOUGH YOU GIVE ME,
YOU KNOW, THE FEELINGS.
WOW.
I HAD NO IDEA
BUT, UH, HEY.
I CAN ALWAYS FIND
ANOTHER MASSEUSE.
REALLY?
YEAH, REALLY.
WHAT?
SUDDENLY, I'M VERY AWARE
THAT I'M NAKED.
OKAY, QUIET DOWN.
MR. SIMON'S BEEN WAITING
FOR... OH, MY GOD.
WHY WASN'T I
OFFERED THAT?
I'D DEFINITELY
PAY MORE FOR THAT.
PHOEBE, WE HAVE
RULES HERE.
THIS IS NOT THAT
KIND OF PLACE.
NO, YEAH, OH, AND I KNOW
BUT THIS ISN'T
HOW IT LOOKS AT ALL
'CAUSE RICK IS,
UM... MY HUSBAND.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, THEN, YOU BETTER
TELL HIS OTHER WIFE
'CAUSE SHE CALLED
THREE TIMES
ASKING WHERE HE IS.
YES, I WILL TELL... HER.
SO YOU DIDN'T
LEAVE THE BANK?
NO...
AND SOMEHOW, WE ENDED UP
WITH A JOINT CHECKING ACCOUNT.
WHAT ARE YOU EVER
GOING TO USE THAT FOR?
TO PAY FOR THE GYM.
HEY.
HEY!
SO, I HAD A GREAT DAY.
RICK AND I HIT IT OFF.
WE STARTED MAKING OUT
AND THEN, MY BOSS WALKED IN
AND FIRED ME FOR BEING A WHORE.
WHAT?
YOU GOT FIRED?
IT'S SO WEIRD.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN FIRED
FROM ANYTHING BEFORE.
SWEETIE.
I JUST STARTED
WALKING AROUND
NOT KNOWING WHAT TO
DO NEXT, YOU KNOW?
I STARTED ASKING
PEOPLE ON THE STREET
IF THEY WANTED MASSAGES.
THEN THESE POLICEMEN
THOUGHT I WAS A WHORE, TOO.
OH!
IT'S REALLY BEEN
A BAD DAY, WHORE-WISE.
( knocking at door )
HEY, DUCK.
IS CHICK HERE?
YEAH...
BUNNY RABBIT.
YOU READY FOR OUR
LAST PRACTICE?
YEAH, BUT I THINK
THE REASON
WE'RE NOT GETTING
THAT SPIN RIGHT
IS BECAUSE
MY APARTMENT'S TOO SMALL.
WANT TO USE OUR PLACE?
NO.
I HAD ANOTHER IDEA.
♪ NIGHT AND DAY ♪
♪ YOU ARE THE ONE ♪
♪ ONLY YOU BENEATH THE MOON ♪
♪ AND UNDER THE SUN ♪
♪ WHETHER NEAR TO ME OR FAR ♪
♪ IT'S NOT MATTER, DARLING,
WHERE YOU ARE ♪
♪ I THINK OF YOU ♪
♪ NIGHT AND DAY. ♪
WE DID IT!
I KNOW! WE DID IT!
HEY, THAT WAS
INCREDIBLE, HUH?
THAT WAS AMAZING!
I MEAN, WE TOTALLY NAILED IT!
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
HEY, LISTEN.
THANKS A LOT, TRIBBIANI.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK AT THE TIME.
I GOT TO CATCH
THE BUS TO THE BALL.
OH. OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
YEAH.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO PRACTICE
THE FOX-TROT AGAIN
OR THE TANGO?
UH, THANKS, BUT NO.
YOU SEE, I THINK I'M READY
TO DANCE WITH GIRLS.
OKAY.
GO GET 'EM, TREEGER.
RIGHT.
HEY, UH...
YOU WANT TO COME?
MARGE HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU COULD DANCE WITH HER.
SHE'S THE SAME SIZE AS ME.
NO. I'M GOOD.
SO, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
SOME GREAT EXPERIENCE HERE.
LET'S SEE.
REASON FOR LEAVING LAST JOB?
YEAH. THEY THOUGHT
I WAS A WHORE.
OKAY.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A CALL
IF ANYTHING COMES UP.
GREAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]